[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Is that how you saw it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "how", "you", "saw", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Originally a little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["Originally", "a", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "But what do you think of the way the governor has gone about this generally?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "way", "the", "governor", "has", "gone", "about", "this", "generally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "He didn't really kind of want to listen to anything.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "did", "n't", "really", "kind", "of", "want", "to", "listen", "to", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vivian"]}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "I mean, Meghan, to put it into perspective for viewers, how many seizures can Vivian have in a day?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "Meghan", ",", "to", "put", "it", "into", "perspective", "for", "viewers", ",", "how", "many", "seizures", "can", "Vivian", "have", "in", "a", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "You know, Vivian on a good day will have, you know, maybe 10 seizures and those are myoclonic seizures.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Vivian", "on", "a", "good", "day", "will", "have", ",", "you", "know", ",", "maybe", "10", "seizures", "and", "those", "are", "myoclonic", "seizures", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Meghan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"], "LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Brian, the reality of the actions that Governor Christie took on Friday, when does that mean that you could actually use edible marijuana for Vivian legally in New Jersey?", "question_tokens": ["Brian", ",", "the", "reality", "of", "the", "actions", "that", "Governor", "Christie", "took", "on", "Friday", ",", "when", "does", "that", "mean", "that", "you", "could", "actually", "use", "edible", "marijuana", "for", "Vivian", "legally", "in", "New", "Jersey", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Well, today it just went -- the conditional veto just got approved by the Senate in New Jersey.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "today", "it", "just", "went", "--", "the", "conditional", "veto", "just", "got", "approved", "by", "the", "Senate", "in", "New", "Jersey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"], "PERSON": ["Christie"], "LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Are you tempted to take Vivian out of New Jersey and go somewhere like Colorado, for example, where it's all completely legal?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "tempted", "to", "take", "Vivian", "out", "of", "New", "Jersey", "and", "go", "somewhere", "like", "Colorado", ",", "for", "example", ",", "where", "it", "'s", "all", "completely", "legal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Jersey", "Colorado"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "And how is she at the moment, would you say, Brian?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "is", "she", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "would", "you", "say", ",", "Brian", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Today she was pretty good.", "answer_tokens": ["Today", "she", "was", "pretty", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brian"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "You did the first nappy change?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "the", "first", "nappy", "change", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "I did the first nappy, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "the", "first", "nappy", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "He seemed very relaxed in that interview and happy to talk?", "question_tokens": ["He", "seemed", "very", "relaxed", "in", "that", "interview", "and", "happy", "to", "talk", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "You were comfortable there?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "comfortable", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "The new, mature dad Prince William?", "question_tokens": ["The", "new", ",", "mature", "dad", "Prince", "William", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "He's extraordinarily appealing.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "extraordinarily", "appealing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "To me, it sounds utterly absurd but what do you think of it?", "question_tokens": ["To", "me", ",", "it", "sounds", "utterly", "absurd", "but", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Well, (INAUDIBLE).", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marissa Mayer"]}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Are you applauding Ms. Mayer for this?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "applauding", "Ms.", "Mayer", "for", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "It was a very unlikely picture in a way for Marissa Mayer because she's very sort of cool and almost Nordic in sort of an aloof beauty and charm and shyness.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "very", "unlikely", "picture", "in", "a", "way", "for", "Marissa", "Mayer", "because", "she", "'s", "very", "sort", "of", "cool", "and", "almost", "Nordic", "in", "sort", "of", "an", "aloof", "beauty", "and", "charm", "and", "shyness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ms. Mayer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Abby, first of all, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Abby", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "ORGAN: Well, better than you last week.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Well", ",", "better", "than", "you", "last", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "``", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Tell me what was going through your mind when this bear was coming towards you?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "what", "was", "going", "through", "your", "mind", "when", "this", "bear", "was", "coming", "towards", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "What was going through my mind was, \"There's a bear attacking me.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "was", "going", "through", "my", "mind", "was", ",", "``", "There", "'s", "a", "bear", "attacking", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "So what made you remember that?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "made", "you", "remember", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, first I ran because I was terrified so I just started running and then it just took me down.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "I", "ran", "because", "I", "was", "terrified", "so", "I", "just", "started", "running", "and", "then", "it", "just", "took", "me", "down", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "When the bear attacked you, what did it actually do to you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "the", "bear", "attacked", "you", ",", "what", "did", "it", "actually", "do", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "When the bear attacked me, it just clawed me and it was like growling and it -- yes, it was scary.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "the", "bear", "attacked", "me", ",", "it", "just", "clawed", "me", "and", "it", "was", "like", "growling", "and", "it", "--", "yes", ",", "it", "was", "scary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "Where were you when this happened, Chris, and what was your reaction when you found out what was going on?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "when", "this", "happened", ",", "Chris", ",", "and", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "found", "out", "what", "was", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "I was inside the house.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "inside", "the", "house", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Did you see the bear?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "the", "bear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "I mean, Abby, when that bear left, that must have been one of the best moments of your life, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "Abby", ",", "when", "that", "bear", "left", ",", "that", "must", "have", "been", "one", "of", "the", "best", "moments", "of", "your", "life", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Yes but it was almost one of the most terrifying.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "but", "it", "was", "almost", "one", "of", "the", "most", "terrifying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Abby"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "How's she going to call you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "she", "going", "to", "call", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "She's had a few and she's lost a few, and she just didn't happen to have one at the time.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "had", "a", "few", "and", "she", "'s", "lost", "a", "few", ",", "and", "she", "just", "did", "n't", "happen", "to", "have", "one", "at", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Are you on Facebook?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "on", "Facebook", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Yes, I'm on Facebook.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'m", "on", "Facebook", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "I mean, you must be loving this, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "must", "be", "loving", "this", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "It's been wonderful.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "wonderful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "I mean, does every prominent black star in America have similar stories to tell?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "does", "every", "prominent", "black", "star", "in", "America", "have", "similar", "stories", "to", "tell", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Oh, I'm sure they do.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "'m", "sure", "they", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Lee, do you think that America is a more or less racist country since Barack Obama became president?", "question_tokens": ["Lee", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "America", "is", "a", "more", "or", "less", "racist", "country", "since", "Barack", "Obama", "became", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Have you yourself suffered that kind of racism?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "yourself", "suffered", "that", "kind", "of", "racism", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Or should they adopt a more conciliatory way of going about dealing with racism?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "should", "they", "adopt", "a", "more", "conciliatory", "way", "of", "going", "about", "dealing", "with", "racism", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "I think that was the reason why I was attracted to the screenplay, because there's several trains of thought on what's the most affective way to go, but what has happened, I think with our youth today is there's been a real disconnect with the civil rights movement and the history of it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "was", "the", "reason", "why", "I", "was", "attracted", "to", "the", "screenplay", ",", "because", "there", "'s", "several", "trains", "of", "thought", "on", "what", "'s", "the", "most", "affective", "way", "to", "go", ",", "but", "what", "has", "happened", ",", "I", "think", "with", "our", "youth", "today", "is", "there", "'s", "been", "a", "real", "disconnect", "with", "the", "civil", "rights", "movement", "and", "the", "history", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Yes sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "What is your view about that debate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "about", "that", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "I think at the end of the day, it's a hard one because it is used, it has become a word that we use affectionately, in play.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "day", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "hard", "one", "because", "it", "is", "used", ",", "it", "has", "become", "a", "word", "that", "we", "use", "affectionately", ",", "in", "play", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]